Always have an exit.
Crime 101 is a crime, thriller film directed by Bart Layton.
When an elusive thief whose high-stakes heists unfold along the iconic 101 freeway in Los Angeles eyes the score of a lifetime, with hopes of this being
his final job, his path collides with a disillusioned insurance broker who is facing her own crossroads, forcing the two to collaborate.
Determined to crack the case, a relentless detective closes in on
the operation, raising the stakes even higher.
Mike Davis, played by Chris Hemsworth.
Sharon, played by Halle Berry.
Detective Lou Lubesnick, played by Mark Ruffalo.
Ormon, played by Barry Keoghan.
Maya, played by Monica Barbaro.
Tillman, played by Corey Hawkins.
Crime 101 is an upcoming crime thriller film
written and directed by Bart Layton.
It is based on the 2020 novella of the same name by Don Winslow.
The film stars Chris Hemsworth, Mark Ruffalo, Barry Keoghan, Monica Barbaro,
Corey Hawkins, Jennifer Jason Leigh, Nick Nolte, and Halle Berry.
Crime 101 is scheduled to be released in the United States by Amazon MGM Studios and
internationally by Sony Pictures Releasing International on February 13, 2026.
The tone is intense.